A Guide to the Land bounty certificates for French and Indian War service from the Virginia Land Office, 1774-1780
Library of Virginia
- Kenty, Miles [cert. 531] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kenty, Miles [cert. 674] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kenty, Miles [cert. 675] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kernal, William (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kincaid, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 3)
- King, John [cert. 255] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- King, John [cert. 1160] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- King, William (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kinkead, John (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kinkead, Thomas [cert. 846] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kinkead, Thomas [cert. 1131] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kinkead, William [cert. 357] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kinkead, William [cert. 847] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kirk, Alexander [see Bell, James] (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Kitchen, John (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Laird, David (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lamb, Archibald (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lamb, John (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lamb, Richard (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lambert, Joseph [see Lightfoot, Francis] (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lambeth, John (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lampton, William (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lane, Dumas (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lane, Littleberry (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lankford, James [cert. 31] (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lankford, James [cert. 1155] (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Larned, Jeremiah (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lawler, Thomas [see Preston, William] (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lawson, John (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lea, John (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Leatherdale, William Jr. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lee, Charles (Box 3, Folder 4)
- LeGrand, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lemay, John (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lemen, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lemen, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lemmons, John (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lewelling, Freeman (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lewis, Charles [cert. 136-138] (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lewis, Charles [cert. 341] (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lewis, John (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lewis, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lewis, Zachary (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lightfoot, Francis (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lindsey, Robert (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Littlepage, John Dickinson (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lloyd, James (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lloyd, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lockhart, Archibald (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lockhart, Charles (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lockhart, James (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Loggins, James (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lohone, Ben (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Long, Henry (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Long, William (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Longes, Daby (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Longest, Richard (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Longest, Timothy (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Looney, Peter (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Losscen, Peter [see Hibdon, James] (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Lovell, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lucas, John (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Luccas, Edward (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lyle, David (Box 3, Folder 5)
- McCarmick, George (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCarmick, William (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCarty, Daniel (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCauley, Niel (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCauley, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McClayland, Daniel (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McClenachan, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McClenachan, John (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McClenanchan, Robert (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McClung, Charles (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McClung, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCollister, James (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCoun, Moses (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCoy, Finley (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCoy, John (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McCutchin, James (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McDonald, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McDonald, Isaac (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McDonald, John [cert. 221] (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McDonald, John [cert. 374] (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McDowell, Hanson (Box 3, Folder 6)
- McFaddin, Pharrel (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McFarland, Daniel (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McGavock, James (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McGehee, James (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McGehee, William (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McGreger, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McKendree, John (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McKensie, John (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McKenzie, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McKenzie, Roderick [see McKenzie, Alexander] (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McLaughlin, Edward (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McLaughlin, James (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McLaughlin, John (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McMahon, John (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McMullin, Edward (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McMullin, John (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McNeill, Angus (Box 3, Folder 7)
- McNeill, Hugh (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Madison, Humphrey (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Madison, John [cert. 921] (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Madison, John (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Mallett, Stephen [see Griffin, Richard] (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Mann, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Mann, William (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Marr, John (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Martain, George (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Martin, Jesse (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Martin, Richard (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Mason, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Mastin, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Matthews, Richard (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Matthews, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Maxey, John (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Maxey, William (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Maxwell, John (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Maxwell, William (Box 3, Folder 8)
- May, James (Box 3, Folder 8)
- May, Jesse (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Mays, John (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Melton, James (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Melton, William (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Mennis, Robert (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Mercer, George (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Mercer, James (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Mercer, John Fenton [see Mercer, George] (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Miller, John (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Miller, Patrick (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Miller, Robert (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Miller, Samuel (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Miller, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Millin, James (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Mills, James (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Mitchell, William (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Monday, John (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Montgomery, John [cert. 1023] (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Montgomery, John [cert. 1200] (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Montgomery, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Montgomery, Samuel (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Montgomery, William Sr. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Moore, Abraham (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Moran, Domnick (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Morgan, Daniel (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Morgan, Haynes (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Morris, Jacob (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Morris, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Morris, William (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Morton, John (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Morton, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Morton, William (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Moss, James (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Moss, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Mothershead, George (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Mourning, Dominick (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Mourning, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Mullican, Tolley [see Preston, William] (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Mulligan, James (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Mullin, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Munday, Reuben (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Murfphey, Edmund (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Murphey, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Murrell, Jeffery (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Murrell, William (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Murry, John (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Muse, George (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Nalle, Martin (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nash, James (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nash, John [cert. 74] (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nash, John [cert. 1134] (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nash, Marvell (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nevils, Henry (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Newberry, Samuel (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Newman, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Newman, Nimrod (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Night, Charles (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nixon, Henry (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Nixon, John (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Noland, James (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Norris, John (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Northcut, William [see Peters, Edmund] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Nourse, Robert (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Offill, John (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Oglesby, William (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Oliver, Benjamin (Box 3, Folder 11)
- O'Neal, Lodowick (Box 3, Folder 11)
- O'Neal, John (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Ormsby, John (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Osbourn, John [see Griffin, Richard] (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Owin, James [see Griffin, Richard] (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Packett, William Stewart (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Page, Alexander (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Parish, James (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Parish, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Parker, Richard (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Parrish, Moses (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Parsinger, Abraham [see Parsinger, Jacob Sr.] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Parsinger, Jacob Sr. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Parsinger, Philip [see Parsinger, Jacob Sr.] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Payne, John (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Peachey, William [cert. 197-198] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Peachey, William [cert. 702-703] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Pearcy, Charles (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Pence, Jacob (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Penix, Edward (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Penix, John (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Penn, Gabriel (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Perrin, John (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Peters, Edmund (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Pettet, Isaac (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Phillips, James (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Phillips, Richard (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Phillips, William [cert. 542] (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Phillips, William [cert. 765] (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Pierce, Jeremiah (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Pigg, Henry (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Pinmore, John (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Plumbley, John (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Poe, David (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Poe, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Poe, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Poindexter, John (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Poindexter, Richard (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Ponston, Richard (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Poo, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Poor, Charles (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Posey, Francis (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Poulter, William (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Powell, Ambrose (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Powell, Benjamin (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Powell, John (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Powell, Simon (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Powell, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Preston, William (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Price, Joseph Shore (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Price, Leonard (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Price, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Provo, William [see Wright, William] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Pryor, John (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Puckett, Drury (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Pullin, Loftus (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Purcell, Edward (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Ragsdale, William (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Raines, Giles (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Ramsay, Augustine (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Ratliff, James [cert. 446] (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Ratliff, James [cert. 435, 472] (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rauthwell, Clabourn (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Ray, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rayburn, Robert (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Reaburne, John (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Read, Hankinson (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Reasoner, Michael (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Reeves, John (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rennold, Benjamin (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rennolds, William (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Reyley, John (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Reynolds, John (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Reynolds, Richard (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rice, George (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rice, Michael (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Richardson, Ezekiel (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Richardson, Turner (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Richeson, Holt (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Riddle, James (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Riddle, Matthew (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Riddle, Richard (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Riley, Francis (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Riley, John (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rion, James (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Ritchey, James (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Ritchie, Patrick [see Turner, John Baker] (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Roberts, Francis (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Roberts, Matthew [cert. 189] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Roberts, Mathew [cert. 562] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Roberts, Morris (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Robertson, James (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Robinson, David [cert. 37] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Robinson, David [cert. 923] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Robinson, George (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Robinson, James (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Robinson, Samuel [see Robinson, George] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Robinson, William [cert. 478] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Robinson, William [cert. 922] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Roe, James (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rogers, William (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rollins, Vincent [see Wright, William] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Ross, Philip (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ross, Robert (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ross, William (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rosser, John (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rouse, John (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Row, Banister (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rowbottom, Matthew (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Roy, James (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Roy, Peter (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rudd, John (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rush, Jacob (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rusher, George (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Russel, James [see Monday, John] (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Russell, William [cert. 936] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Russell, William [cert. 194] (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rutherford, Robert (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ryalty, Daniel (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ryan, James (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ryley, Barney (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Sale, John (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sallard, John (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sallis, Nicholas (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sallmons, Jacob (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sample, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sampson, John (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Samuel, James (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sanders, John [cert. 71] (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sanders, John [cert. 487] (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sanders, Robert (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sanders, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sandren, William (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sansome, Richard (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Satterwhite, James (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Saunders, Thomas [see Preston, William] (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Saunders, William (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Savage, John (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sayer, Alexander (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sayers, David (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sayers, William (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Scott, Charles (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Scott, Edward (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Scott, Francis (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Scott, Nicholas (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Scott, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Scott, William (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Seaman, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Self, Francis (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Self, Jeremiah (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Shackleford, Henry (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shadow, Ludowick (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Sharp, Jacob (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shaw, James (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Sheal, Arnold (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Sheilds, John (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Sheilds, William (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shelby, Evan [cert. 81-84] (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shelby, Evan [cert. 237] (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shelby, John (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shelton, John (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Sheppard, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shepperson, John (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shepperson, William (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Sherington, Robert [see Wright, William] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Sherley, James (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Sherly, Jervice (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Sherly, Walter (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shewin, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shiflett, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shingleton, John (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Simonds, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Simpson, Daniel (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Simpson, Solomon (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Simpson, William (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Sims, George (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Skillern, George (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Skillern, William [cert. 206] (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Skillern, William [cert. 928] (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Slaughter, George (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Small, Mathew (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smallman, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, Charles (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, Francis (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, James (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, John [cert. 216] (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, John [cert. 287] (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, John [cert. 571] (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, John [cert. 624] (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, Nicholas [see Preston, William] (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Smith, Robert (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, Stephen (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smith, William (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smither, William [cert. 441] (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Smither, William, Sr. [cert. 522] (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Sorrell, William (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Sparks, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Speake, George (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Sprigg, Edward (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Spurr, William (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stadler, John (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Standley, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stanley, John (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stanton, Robert (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Staunton, Richard (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Steel, Henry (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Steelman, James [see Preston, William] (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Stephen, Adam (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stephenson, Hugh (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stephenson, John [cert. 904] (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stephenson, John [cert. 1345] (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stevens, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stewart, Alexander (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stewart, David (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stewart, William (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stoggle, Ambros (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stonford, David (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stricker, John (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Strong, John (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Strong, Sherwood [see Strong, John] (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stubblefield, George (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stubbs, Butler (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Summers, John (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Suter, Charles [see Rion, James] (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Sutton, Edward [cert. 259] (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Sutton, Edward [cert. 415] (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Swearengen, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Talbott, Haly (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Tatham, John (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Taylor, George, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Taylor, James [cert. 641] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Taylor, James [cert. 1106] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Taylor, John (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Taylor, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Teater, George [cert. 867] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Teater, George [cert. 882] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Temple, Benjamin [cert. 623] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Temple, Benjamin [cert. 1276] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Terry, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Terry, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Terry, William (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thomas, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thompson, Anthony (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thompson, Archibald (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thompson, Charles (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thompson, David (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thompson, James (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thompson, John (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thompson, William (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thomson, William (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thornton, George (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thorp, John [see Thorp, William] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thorp, John [see Thorp, William] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thorp, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Thorp, William (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Throckmorton, Gaberil (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Throckmorton, Gabriel (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Tilman, Daniel (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Timberlake, Epaphroditus (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Timberlake, Henry (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Timberlake, Richard [see Thorp, William] (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Tinder, James (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tinsley, William (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tomkies, Charles (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tommy, Matthew (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Townsend, Henry (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Travis, Charles [see Hall, William] (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Traylor, John (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tredway, John (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Trigg, John (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Truman, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tunley, John (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Turner, Benjamin (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Turner, Charles (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Turner, George (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Turner, James (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Turner, John Baker (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Turner, William (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tutt, William (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Twopence, James [cert. 463] (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Twopence, James [cert. 464] (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tygert, John (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tyler, Francis (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Underwood, George (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Upton, Thomas (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Vachob, John (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Vanbushkirk, Michael (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Vanmeter, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Vass, Reuben [cert. 545-549] (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Vass, Reuben [cert. 634-637] (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Vaughan, George (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Vaughtor, William (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Vernon, Richard (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Wade, Andrew (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Wade, John Utley (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Wagner, Edmund (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Walden, James (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Walker, Asaph [see Peters, Edmund] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Walker, Henry (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Walker, John (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Walker, Thomas [cert. 36] (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Walker, Thomas [cert. 1182] (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Walker, William (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Wansley, William (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ward, Edward (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ward, James (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ward, Samuel (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ward, William [cert. 203] (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ward, William [cert. 891] (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ward, William [cert. 1294] (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Warner, John (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Watkins, Philip (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Watson, William (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Watts, Charles (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Watts, Samuel (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Watts, William [see Matthews, Thomas] (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Waugh, Alexander Jr. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Webb, Julian (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Webb, Martin (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Webster, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Weedon, George (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wells, James (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Weltshire, Richard (Box 5, Folder 4)
- West, George (Box 5, Folder 4)
- West, John, Jr. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Whayne, Humphrey (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Whayne, William [see Whayne, Humphrey] (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wheeden, Nathan (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wheeley, Benjamin (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wheelor, John (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wheelor, William (Box 5, Folder 4)
- White, Augustine (Box 5, Folder 4)
- White, Chapman (Box 5, Folder 4)
- White, Elisha (Box 5, Folder 4)
- White, George (Box 5, Folder 4)
- White, Samuel, Jr. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- White, William (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Whitlock, Achillis (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Whitlow, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wiley, John [cert. 946] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wiley, John [cert. 1076] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wiley, Peter [cert. 947] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wiley, Peter [cert. 1092] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wilkerson, Edward (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wilkinson, James (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Williams, Jacob (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Williams, James (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Williams, John [cert. 34] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Williams, John [cert. 188] (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Williamson, Richard (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Williamson, Smith (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Willis, Edward (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Willis, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wills, Justinian (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wilson, Peter (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Winslow, Benjamin (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wolverton, John (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Woodrum, John (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wooton, John (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wooton, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wright, John (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Wright, William (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Young, James (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Young, John [cert. 926] (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Young, John [cert. 978] (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Young, Samuel (Box 5, Folder 6)